Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files H
    - Hutchinson, Earl Ofari (Box A-60, Folder 187)
      Also one postcard.
    - Hutchinson, Ernest (Box A-60, Folder 188)
    - Hutchinson, Eulynda (Box A-60, Folder 189)
      Three velox prints.
    - Hutchinson, J.B. (Rev.) (Box A-60, Folder 190)
    - Hutchinson, James (Box A-60, Folder 191)
    - Hutchinson, Joe (Box A-60, Folder 192)
    - Hutchinson, Keri-Beth (Box A-60, Folder 193)
    - Hutchinson, Leigh Ann (Box A-60, Folder 194)
      Note on folder: "See Mr. + Mrs. Wm. D Hutchinson"
    - Hutchinson, Leslie (Box A-60, Folder 195)
    - Hutchinsn, Niki (Box A-60, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: Joseph Griffith
    - Hutchinson, Paul (Box A-60, Folder 197)
    - Hutchinson, Paulett (Box A-60, Folder 198)
    - Hutchinson, Philip S. (Rev.) (Box A-60, Folder 199)
    - Hutchinson, Roger (Box A-60, Folder 200)
    - Hutchinson, Viola (Box A-60, Folder 201)
    - Hutchinson, William (Box A-60, Folder 202)
    - Hutchinson, Wm D. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-60, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial
    - Hutson, Barbara (Box A-60, Folder 204)
    - Hutson, Jean B. (Box A-60, Folder 205)
      Also one magazine clipping.
    - Hutson, Leroy (Box A-60, Folder 206)
      Back of one print notes: "Kluxers couldn't scare 'em."
    - Hutson, Willie (Box A-60, Folder 207)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Hardy
    - Hutto, M.B. (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 208)
      Note on folder: "See Dr. Claude Ferebee."
    - Hutton, Geneva (Box A-60, Folder 209)
    - Hutton, Hank (Box A-60, Folder 210)
    - Hutton, Lee A. (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 211)
    - Hutton-Mills, T. (Box A-60, Folder 212)
    - Hyacinth Club (Box A-60, Folder 213)
      Also five negatives (12 images total).
    - Hyacinthe, Hector (Box A-60, Folder 214)
      Photographer if identified: Monclova
    - Hyatt, David (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 215)
    - Hyatt, Esther (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 216)
    - Hyatt, Margaret (Box A-60, Folder 217)
      Also two negatives (three images total).
    - Hyde, Kavanzo (Box A-60, Folder 218)
    - Hyde-White, Wilfrid (Box A-60, Folder 219)
    - Hyland, Pamela (Box A-60, Folder 220)
    - Hylton, Arnold J. (Box A-60, Folder 221)
    - Hylton, Carmen (Box A-60, Folder 222)
    - Hylton, Nola (Box A-60, Folder 223)
    - Hyman, Dick (Box A-60, Folder 224)
    - Hyman, Earle (Box A-60, Folder 225)
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos, International News Photos
    - Hyman, Ernest (Box A-60, Folder 226)
    - Hyman, Fracaswell (Box A-60, Folder 227)
    - Hyman, George (Box A-60, Folder 228)
    - Hyman, Grace (Box A-60, Folder 229)
    - Hyman, Leo (Box A-60, Folder 230)
    - Hyman, Mark (Box A-60, Folder 231)
      One print has single-leaf press release attached.
    - Hyman, Phyllis (Box A-60, Folder 232)
      Also three velox prints stuck together. One print has press release (five leaves) attached with staple on border.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bryan D. Hall, Juanita M. Cole, Allen Morgan Photo,
    - Hyman, Timmy (Box A-60, Folder 233)
    - Hyman, Violet (Box A-60, Folder 234)
    - Hymes, Lulu Mae (Box A-60, Folder 235)
    - Hynes, Mamie (Box A-60, Folder 236)
    - Hynes, Patricia M. (Box A-60, Folder 237)
      Print has carbonscript press release (two leaves) attached with staples on border.
    - Hynes, Vera (Box A-60, Folder 238)
    - Hypps, Irene C. (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 239)
      Photographer if identified: Frank Brown's Photos
    - Hyslop, Bebe L. (Miss) (Box A-60, Folder 240)
      Also two negatives (two images total).
    - Hyson, Captain (Box A-60, Folder 241)
    - Hyson, Juanita (Box A-60, Folder 242)
    - Hyther, Isabelle F. (Mrs.) (Box A-60, Folder 243)
  - Subject Files I
    - "I Sought My Brother" (Box A-60, Folder 244)
    - Iacocca, Lee A. (Box A-60, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick
    - Iakovos, Archbishop (Box A-60, Folder 246)
    - Iandoli, Louis (Box A-60, Folder 247)
    - Ibarra, Barbara A. (Box A-60, Folder 248)
      Photographer if identified: University News Bureau
    - Ibiam, Akaun (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 249)
    - Ibian, Francis (Sir) (Box A-60, Folder 250)
      Print has single typescript leaf adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: International News Photos
    - Ibiis (Group) (Box A-60, Folder 251)
    - Ibis (Box A-60, Folder 252)
      See "Ibiis (Group)"
    - Ibrahim, Abdullah (Box A-60, Folder 253)
    - Ibrahim, Abdullah (Box A-60, Folder 254)
    - Ice Skating (Box A-60, Folder 255)
    - Ickes, Harold L. (Box A-60, Folder 256)
    - Id Club (Box A-60, Folder 257)
    - Idi, Joseph Lawe (Box A-60, Folder 258)
      Print is mounted on board and has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
    - Idlett, Ben (Box A-60, Folder 259)
    - Idlett, Mary (Box A-60, Folder 260)
    - Ifill, Carson (Box A-60, Folder 261)
    - Ifill, Diane (Box A-60, Folder 262)
    - Ifill, Elaine (Box A-60, Folder 263)
    - Ifill, Evelyn (Box A-60, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Hawkins
    - Ifill, O. Urcille (Box A-60, Folder 265)
    - Ifill Sr., O. Urcille (Rev.) (Box A-60, Folder 266)
      Photographer if identified: Foto Wallace
    - Ifill, Percy (Box A-60, Folder 267)
    - Ifill, Percy (Mrs.) (Box A-60, Folder 268)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Harris Photo
    - Ifter, Mirus (Box A-60, Folder 269)
    - Iglehart, James (Box A-60, Folder 270)
    - Ignacio-Pinto, Louis H.E.M. (Box A-60, Folder 271)
      Both prints have single typescript leaves attached.
    - Igus, Darron (Box A-60, Folder 272)
    - Igus, Darrow (Box A-60, Folder 273)
    - Ike, Johnny (Box A-60, Folder 274)
    - Ike & His Drummers (Box A-60, Folder 275)
    - Ike and Tina Turner Revue (Box A-60, Folder 276)
    - Ike (Rev.) (Box A-60, Folder 277)
      Two prints have single-leaf press releases attached.
    - Ikhlas (Group) (Box A-60, Folder 278)
      Also one velox print. Short text written in pen on verso.
    - Ikiche, Richard (Box A-60, Folder 279)
    - Ikpe, Ernest (Box A-60, Folder 280)
      single-leaf press release.
    - Ilaw, Marianne (Box A-60, Folder 281)
    - Illedge, Eric (Box A-60, Folder 282)
    - Illery, Alma (Dr.) (Box A-60, Folder 283)
      One print has typescript press release (three leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Illidge, Eric (Box A-60, Folder 284)
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams, Harris Photo, James Gilbert
    - Illidge, Yvonne (Box A-60, Folder 285)
    - Illma, Viola (Box A-60, Folder 286)
      Photographer if identified: Karl Von Romerheim
    - Illori, Solomon Gbadegesin (Box A-60, Folder 287)
    - Illustra-shuns, The (Box A-60, Folder 288)
    - Illveca, Jorge E. (Box A-60, Folder 289)
    - "Imagination" (Group) (Box A-60, Folder 290)
    - Iman (Box A-60, Folder 291)
    - Imarah, Joseph (Box A-60, Folder 292)
    - Imbert, Earl A. (Box A-60, Folder 293)
    - Imes, G. Lake (Mrs.) (Box A-60, Folder 294)
      Photographer if identified: Wiseman Photo
    - Imes, G. Lake (Box A-60, Folder 295)
      Photographer if identified: Office of War Information
    - Imes, Hope (Box A-60, Folder 296)
    - Imes, Wendell (Box A-60, Folder 297)
    - Imes, William L. (Rev.) (Box A-60, Folder 298)
    - Imnan, William (Rudy) (Box A-60, Folder 299)
    - Impelleteri, Mrs. Vincent (Box A-60, Folder 300)
    - Impelliteri, Vincent R. (Box A-60, Folder 301)
    - Imperials (Little Anthony) (Box A-60, Folder 302)
      Note on folder: Singing group
    - Imrie, Kathy (Box A-60, Folder 303)
    - Impressions, The (Box A-61, Folder 1)
      Three prints have staples on border. One print is cut out and mounted on paper.
    - Impulse (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 2)
    - Imrie, Kathy (Box A-61, Folder 3)
    - In Crowd (Box A-61, Folder 4)
    - Inca (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 5)
    - Ince, Robert W. (Box A-61, Folder 6)
    - Ince, William (Box A-61, Folder 7)
    - Independents (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 8)
    - Independent Black Opera Singers (Box A-61, Folder 9)
    - Indians (Box A-61, Folder 10)
    - Industrial Community Center (Box A-61, Folder 11)
    - Infantry (Box A-61, Folder 12)
    - Infascinations (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 13)
      Note on folder: "Vocal Group."
    - "Infinity Factory" (Box A-61, Folder 14)
    - Ingberg, Bridgett (Box A-61, Folder 15)
    - Inge, Florence Irene (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 16)
    - Ingleton, Carlton (Box A-61, Folder 17)
    - Ingenious Americans (Box A-61, Folder 18)
    - Ingersoll, Jeremiah C. (Box A-61, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: Rapid News Service
    - Ingersoll, Ralph (Box A-61, Folder 20)
    - Ingersoll, Raymond C. (Box A-61, Folder 21)
    - Ingraham, Hollis N. (Box A-61, Folder 22)
    - Ingram, Albert (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 23)
    - Ingram, Booker T. (Box A-61, Folder 24)
    - Ingram, Chas. (Sgt. 1st class) (Box A-61, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: International News Photos, Keystone Pictures Inc.
    - Ingram, Dan (Box A-61, Folder 26)
    - Ingram, Garnett Atkins (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 27)
    - Ingram, Germaine (Box A-61, Folder 28)
    - Ingram, Kellam (Box A-61, Folder 29)
    - Ingram, Luther (Box A-61, Folder 30)
    - Ingram, Milroy (Box A-61, Folder 31)
      Note on folder: "See Ruth Attaway."
    - Ingram, Reginald (Box A-61, Folder 32)
    - Ingram, Rex (Box A-61, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Floyd G. Snelson, WPA Federal Theatre Photos
    - Ingram, Rex (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 34)
    - Ingram, Robert (Mr. + Mrs. & family) (Box A-61, Folder 35)
    - Ingram, Thelma Horton (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 36)
    - Ingram, Sheila (Box A-61, Folder 37)
      Photographer if identified: Al-Hakim Al-Mutlaq
    - Ingram, Tommy (Box A-61, Folder 38)
    - Ingram, Walter (Box A-61, Folder 39)
    - Inman + Ira (Box A-61, Folder 40)
    - Inmates (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 41)
    - Innervisions (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 42)
    - Innis, Al (Box A-61, Folder 43)
    - Innis, Charles (Box A-61, Folder 44)
    - Innis, Charles (Box A-61, Folder 45)
    - Innis, Eleanor (Box A-61, Folder 46)
    - Innis, Ruth (Box A-61, Folder 47)
    - Innis, Lorraine Leonore & Ismay (Box A-61, Folder 48)
    - Inniss, Roy (Box A-61, Folder 49)
      Back of folder reads: "Innnis, Alexander (Mr. & Mrs.)"
    - Innis, Roy (Box A-61, Folder 50)
    - Innis, Roy (Box A-61, Folder 51)
      Also one velox print. One print has staple in border; one has single-leaf press release and single photocopied leaf newspaper article attached with staple.
    - Inniss, Verneil (Box A-61, Folder 52)
    - "Innkeepers, The" (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 53)
    - Innman, Annette (Box A-61, Folder 54)
    - Insdorf, Annette (Box A-61, Folder 55)
    - Insernia, Agnes (Box A-61, Folder 56)
    - Insignias (Box A-61, Folder 57)
      Ink drawings mounted on board.
    - Instant Funk (Box A-61, Folder 58)
    - Interamerican Life Corp. (Box A-61, Folder 59)
    - Interboro Crescents (Box A-61, Folder 60)
    - Interfaith Hospital (Box A-61, Folder 61)
      One print has single typescript leaf attached with paperclip. Note on folder: (See also Dr. Thomas Matthew)
      Photographer if identified: Tex Harris, Harris Photo
    - Interfaith Humani Club (Box A-61, Folder 62)
    - International Cotillion (Box A-61, Folder 63)
      Both prints have single-leaf press releases attached.
    - International Mannequins (Box A-61, Folder 64)
      Photographer if identified: Edwin Hamza
    - International Sweethearts of Rhythm (Box A-61, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: United Service Organizations Inc.
    - International Womens Guild (Box A-61, Folder 66)
    - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity (Box A-61, Folder 67)
    - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity (Box A-61, Folder 68)
      Also one velox print. One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Harris Photo, News Voice International, Omar Kharem
    - Intrigue (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 69)
      Back reads: "Flygirls' Boyfriends."
    - Intigues, The (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 70)
    - Intruders, The (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 71)
      One print has press release (three leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Inventor, Lord (Box A-61, Folder 72)
    - Ioshewitz, Morris (Box A-61, Folder 73)
    - Ipi, Tombi (Box A-61, Folder 74)
    - Ipke, Ernest (Box A-61, Folder 75)
    - Irakles, Rene (Box A-61, Folder 76)
    - Iran (Box A-61, Folder 77)
    - Irby, Dean (Box A-61, Folder 78)
    - Ireland, Charles (Dr.) (Box A-61, Folder 79)
    - Irish, Bernice (Box A-61, Folder 80)
    - Irish, Carleton P. (Box A-61, Folder 81)
    - Irish, Doris (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 82)
    - Irish, Ned (Box A-61, Folder 83)
    - Irish, Isabelle (Box A-61, Folder 84)
    - Irish, William (Box A-61, Folder 85)
    - Irons, Arthur (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 86)
      Print has single typescript leaf attached.
    - Irons, Claude (Box A-61, Folder 87)
    - Irons, Edward D. (Box A-61, Folder 88)
      One print is mounted on cardstock; one has single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Agency for International Development, Scurlock
    - Irons, Hubert Jr. (Box A-61, Folder 89)
    - Irons, Jackie (Box A-61, Folder 90)
    - Irons, Josephine (Box A-61, Folder 91)
    - Irrisistible Gospel Charts (Box A-61, Folder 92)
    - Irvin, Anita (Box A-61, Folder 93)
      Note on folder: "See Mrs. Cleveland Bowser."
    - Irvin, Cal (Box A-61, Folder 94)
    - Irvin, Dellia (Box A-61, Folder 95)
      Note on folder: "See Atty. Paul C. Perkins."
    - Irvin, Edward Giles (Box A-61, Folder 96)
    - Irvin, Fed (Box A-61, Folder 97)
    - Irvin, Leon (Box A-61, Folder 98)
    - Irvin, Walter (Box A-61, Folder 99)
      Also one newspaper clipping. One print has a single typescript leaf description of crime case attached.
      Photographer if identified: Keystone Pictures Inc.
    - Irvin, Willie (Box A-61, Folder 100)
    - Irvine, Weldon J. Jr. (Box A-61, Folder 101)
    - Irvine, Weldon (Box A-61, Folder 102)
    - Irving, Barbara (Box A-61, Folder 103)
    - Irving, Carol (Box A-61, Folder 104)
    - Irving, H. Clay (Dr. & Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 105)
    - Irving, George Ross (Box A-61, Folder 106)
      Also one computer-printed typescript card with photo which reads "Introducing George Ross Irving..." on verso.
    - Irving, Jacqueline (Box A-61, Folder 107)
    - Irving, James (Box A-61, Folder 108)
    - Irving, Jane T. (Box A-61, Folder 109)
    - Irving, Jessie Mae (Box A-61, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: John Bowen
    - Irving, Julius (Box A-61, Folder 111)
    - Irving, Richard E. (Dr.) (Box A-61, Folder 112)
    - Irving, Robert (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 113)
    - Irving, Tyree (Box A-61, Folder 114)
    - Irwin, Barry (Box A-61, Folder 115)
    - Irwin, Leon (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 116)
    - Irvis, K. Leroy (Box A-61, Folder 117)
    - Irwin, Patricia (Box A-61, Folder 118)
    - Isaacs, Albert E. (Box A-61, Folder 119)
    - Isaac, Alfred (Rev. & Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 120)
    - Isaac, Deborah (Box A-61, Folder 121)
    - Isaac, Ephraim (Box A-61, Folder 122)
    - Isaac, Leon (Box A-61, Folder 123)
    - Isaac, Mel (Box A-61, Folder 124)
    - Isaacs, Archie (Box A-61, Folder 125)
    - Isaacs, Irving E. (Mr.) (Box A-61, Folder 126)
    - Isaacs, Ned (Box A-61, Folder 127)
    - Isaacs, Robert (Box A-61, Folder 128)
    - Stanley, M. Isaacs (Box A-61, Folder 129)
      Also three paper stereotype matrices. One print has single typescript leaf attached on verso.
    - Isaacs, Will (Box A-61, Folder 130)
    - Isaacs, Wills O. (Box A-61, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Hawkins
    - Isalquez, Dulce (Box A-61, Folder 132)
    - Isis & Assoc. (Ms.) (Box A-61, Folder 133)
    - Isler, C. (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 134)
      Prints are stuck together with paste. One print is stuck to folder.
    - Isler, Jacques (Box A-61, Folder 135)
    - Isler, Janet (Box A-61, Folder 136)
    - Isley, Rosetta (Box A-61, Folder 137)
    - Isley Brothers (Box A-61, Folder 138)
      Also two velox prints. One print and one velox print have paste on verso.
    - Ismail, Sacred (Box A-61, Folder 139)
      One print has reads "Joseph Ismail" on verso; other print reads "Isamail A. Razack" on verso.
    - Ismom, G. (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 140)
    - Ison, Joe (Box A-61, Folder 141)
    - Israel, Jacob James (Box A-61, Folder 142)
    - Israel + Israelites (Box A-61, Folder 143)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Lloyd Yearwood
    - Isaacs, Estelle (Box A-61, Folder 144)
    - Itals (Group) (Box A-61, Folder 145)
      Print has single typescript leaf attached with staple on border.
    - Iturbi, Jose (Box A-61, Folder 146)
      Print also has typescript press release (two leaves) attached with staple.
    - Isum, Rachael (Box A-61, Folder 147)
    - Ither, Henry (Box A-61, Folder 148)
    - Iushewitz, Morris (Box A-61, Folder 149)
    - Iuvalle, Jimmy and Archie Williams (Box A-61, Folder 150)
    - Ivan, Assemblyman (Box A-61, Folder 151)
    - Iverson, Alan (Box A-61, Folder 152)
    - Ivery, Kathryn (Box A-61, Folder 153)
    - Ives, Irving (Box A-61, Folder 154)
    - Ives, Ronnie (Box A-61, Folder 155)
    - Ivey, Mary (Box A-61, Folder 156)
    - Ivey, Rodney (Box A-61, Folder 157)
    - Ivey, Walter (Box A-61, Folder 158)
      Print is mounted on paper which reads "To Strike on PWA Houses" on verso.
    - Ivey, Waverly (Box A-61, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: Banner & Greif
    - Ivory, Billye (Box A-61, Folder 160)
    - Ivory, Delores (Box A-61, Folder 161)
    - Ivory, Kenneth (Box A-61, Folder 162)
      One velox print mounted on paper.
    - Ivory, Lee (Box A-61, Folder 163)
    - Ivory, Marcellius (Box A-61, Folder 164)
      Photographer if identified: UAW Solidarity
    - Ivy, Carol (Box A-61, Folder 165)
    - Ivy, James W. (Box A-61, Folder 166)
    - Ivy, Jeanette (Box A-61, Folder 167)
    - Ix, Robert B. (Box A-61, Folder 168)
      Photographer if identified: Earl M. Silver
    - Iyalla, H. E. Joe (Box A-61, Folder 169)
    - Iyanla (Box A-61, Folder 170)
    - Izulu Children's Theatre (Box A-61, Folder 171)
      One print has two images.
  - Subject Files J
    - Jabon, Antoine (Mme.) (Box A-61, Folder 172)
    - Jachill, Leon (Box A-61, Folder 173)
    - Jack & Jills Club (Box A-61, Folder 174)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Carter, King Photographers, Rufus Merritt, G. Leonard Bing, Gill Photographers, Russ Carter, Carmel Studios, James C. Campbell,
    - Jack, Shirley (Box A-61, Folder 175)
    - Jack, Hulan E. (Box A-61, Folder 176)
      12 prints have staples on border. Also one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Cecil Layne, James C. Campbell, Nate Silverstein, Lloyd Yearwood, Eli Aaron, United Press International Mallory Photo, F. Carl Goodison, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Thomas R. Pinchman, Tex Harris, David McAdams
    - Jack, Hulan (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 177)
    - Jack, Raymond (Box A-61, Folder 178)
    - Jackett, Illinois (Box A-61, Folder 179)
    - Jackie, Eleanor (Box A-61, Folder 180)
    - Jackman, Harold (Box A-61, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Rapid News Photo
    - Jackman, F. E. (Box A-61, Folder 182)
    - Jackman, Gary (Box A-61, Folder 183)
    - Jackman, Ivie (Box A-61, Folder 184)
    - Jackman, Lawrence Jr. (Box A-61, Folder 185)
    - Jacko, Edward (Box A-61, Folder 186)
    - Jacko, Shirley (Box A-61, Folder 187)
    - Jackowski, Bill (Box A-61, Folder 188)
      Print has single typescript press release attached.
    - Jackson, A. (Box A-61, Folder 189)
    - Jackson, Abby (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 190)
    - Jackson, Ada B. (Box A-61, Folder 191)
    - Jackson, Ada V. (Box A-61, Folder 192)
    - Jackson, Al (Box A-61, Folder 193)
    - Jackson, Al Jr. (Box A-61, Folder 194)
    - Jackson, Alanson (Box A-61, Folder 195)
    - Jackson, Albert (Box A-61, Folder 196)
    - Jackson, Alex (Box A-61, Folder 197)
    - (Box A-61, Folder 198)
    - Jackson, Alexander L. (Box A-61, Folder 199)
    - Jackson, Alice (Box A-61, Folder 200)
    - Jackson, Allan C. (Box A-61, Folder 201)
    - Jackson, Allison (Box A-61, Folder 202)
    - Jackson, Alvin (Box A-61, Folder 203)
    - Jackson, Andrew (Box A-61, Folder 204)
    - Jackson, Andrew (Box A-61, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: John E. Hopkins
    - Jackson, Andrew F. (Box A-61, Folder 206)
    - Jackson, Ann (Box A-61, Folder 207)
    - Jackson, Ann (Box A-61, Folder 208)
    - Jackson, Anna Lee (Box A-61, Folder 209)
    - Jackson, Anne (Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 210)
    - Jackson, Arie (Box A-61, Folder 211)
    - Jackson, Arline (Box A-61, Folder 212)
    - Jackson, Art (Box A-61, Folder 213)
    - Jackson, Arthur (Box A-61, Folder 214)
    - Jackson, Arthur H. K. (Guild) (Box A-61, Folder 215)
      Single ms. leaf and also one typescript leaf.
    - Jackson, Audrey (Box A-61, Folder 216)
    - Jackson, Augustine (Box A-61, Folder 217)
    - Jackson, Barbara (Box A-61, Folder 218)
      Also one velox print. One print has single typescript leaf letter attached with staple on border.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Jackson, Barbara J. (Box A-61, Folder 219)
    - Jackson, Ben (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-61, Folder 220)
    - Jackson, Benj J. (Dr.) (Box A-61, Folder 221)
      Photographer if identified: Herman S. Paris
    - Jackson, Bernard (Box A-61, Folder 222)
      Also five velox prints. One print has single typescript press release attached on verso. One print is cut out and mounted on paper.
    - Jackson, Bernie (Box A-61, Folder 223)
    - Jackson, Besshunter (Box A-61, Folder 224)
    - Jackson, Bessie (Box A-61, Folder 225)
      Print has single ms. leaf attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Williams Photography
    - Jackson, Betty (Box A-61, Folder 226)
    - Jackson, Andrew P. (Box A-61, Folder 227)
    - Jackson, Beverly (Box A-61, Folder 228)
    - Jackson, Billy (Box A-61, Folder 229)
    - Jackson, Bluford (Box A-61, Folder 230)
    - Jackson, Bob (Box A-61, Folder 231)
    - Jackson, Bo (Box A-61, Folder 232)
    - Jackson, Bobbie Jean (Box A-61, Folder 233)
    - Jackson, Bonnie (Box A-61, Folder 234)
      Print has carbonscript press release (seven leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Jackson, Bruce (Box A-61, Folder 235)
    - Jackson, "Bull Moose" (Box A-61, Folder 236)
    - Jackson, Bumpy (Box A-61, Folder 237)
    - Jackson, Burt (Box A-61, Folder 238)
    - Jackson, C. J. (Box A-61, Folder 239)
    - Jackson, Calvin (Box A-61, Folder 240)
    - Jackson, Carol (Box A-61, Folder 241)
    - Jackson, Carolyn (Box A-61, Folder 242)
    - Jackson, Carrington B. (Box A-61, Folder 243)
    - Jackson, Catherine (Box A-61, Folder 244)
    - Jackson, Cedric Dunbar (Box A-61, Folder 245)
    - Jackson, Charisse (Box A-61, Folder 246)
    - Jackson, Charles (Box A-61, Folder 247)
    - Jackson, Charles (Box A-61, Folder 248)
    - Jackson, Charles (Box A-61, Folder 249)
      Photographer if identified: E. McDonald Photographer
    - Jackson, Charles (Box A-61, Folder 250)
    - Jackson, Charlie (Box A-61, Folder 251)
    - Jackson, Christina (Box A-61, Folder 252)
      Photographer if identified: Frederick A. Schroeder
    - Jackson, Chubby (Box A-61, Folder 253)
    - Jackson, Chuck (Box A-61, Folder 254)
    - Jackson, Clarence Sr. (Box A-61, Folder 255)
    - Jackson, Cleolia (Box A-61, Folder 256)
      Print is mounted on board.
    - Jackson, Cliff (Box A-61, Folder 257)
    - Jackson, Clyde (Box A-61, Folder 258)
    - Jackson, Cornelious (Box A-61, Folder 259)